All right, y'all. Bitcoin currently in
Chop City, but this morning we had the
CPI data come out. And guess what? It
was exactly what everybody expected it
was going to be. So, what does this mean
for Bitcoin? Is it bullish? Is it
bearish? What can we expect as Bitcoin
is currently consolidating near key
levels? We're going to be breaking it
down for you today. So, like, subscribe,
get on the treadmill, click the bell for
notifications. We're bringing you the
juiciest Bitcoin updates here on
YouTube. So, firstly, let's discuss the
CPI data. Here's the thing. It's not
necessarily bearish because it didn't
surprise people by coming in higher than
expected, but it's also not bullish
because people were already expecting
these numbers. And as the news has come
out, Bitcoin has gotten a pretty large
move to the downside. A big old pump and
dump. Classic buy the rumor, sell the
news event, as you can see here on the
chart. So, what are the next major
setups for Bitcoin? Are we bullish or
are we bearish? Well, as I always say,
not just me, but all the best traders,
they always say, "Show me the chart and
I'll rip out a fart." Well, maybe they
don't say that, but but I say that. All
the cool traders say that, and I'm
pretty cool, right?
So, here's the deal. Over the weekend,
Bitcoin was forming this disgustingly
bearish looking channel. And if you saw
my stream on Sunday, I was saying,
"Look, if we lose this trend line, we're
most likely going to come down and grab
all the liquidity from down below." And
that's exactly what has happened. If we
also take a look here at the Fibonacci
pull from the local low at 622 to the
local high, you can see that we did get
a bounce right between the zone of the
Fibonacci golden pocket and the 786. All
right, we're getting a bounce from there
in a little bit of a long trade from
there right now. And if we take a look
at the oscillator market cipher B, we
can see that as we came down to hit this
level, it was a very nice looking low.
We had a very juicy bullish divergence,
momentum getting higher as the price
getting lower, giving us the juicy
uneven butt cheek pattern. and we did
get a move to the upside. Obviously, CPI
news gave us a move back down. So, what
am I currently looking at here? Well, I
would be looking at, first of all,
obviously, if we come down to back test
around the $635,000 level, I might
actually compound my open long. But for
a new long trade, I'd actually be
interested in a little bit of a lower
level here. And I'll tell you why.
because yes, we're bouncing from the
Fibonacci golden pocket, but if we take
a look at all the volume that's traded
here, you can see that we have rejected
from the PC of the range, which means
the highest probability is we come down
just below 63K.
So really, the next long trade that I
would be interested is coming down to
that $63,000ish
zone, getting a little dip, diddly dupe
below, and then a nice reclaim above,
which gives us a clear entry trigger,
stop-loss, and then target back to the
top of the range. Why would I target
back to the top of the range? Because if
we come down there, we have to think how
would the oscillator look. We would have
the most insanely bullish divergence
here. We would have 1 2 three cheeks
giving us the tri- cheekular formation
of juicy goodness at the bottom of a
range. That is what you want to look
for. Now, of course, if for example, we
don't see anything juicy down there and
we just fall right through. What does
that mean? Well, we cannot ignore the
fact that we have massive amounts of
liquidity coming all the way down to
here. Right? This is really what we have
going on here. If we're going to lose
the value area low, we're most likely
going to come down lower to take all the
liquidity of this entire chunk. Now, if
we pull the Fibonacci from the macro low
to the macro high, and when I say macro,
I'm talking about our our range from
June, July, and so far August. You can
see we have a beautiful confluence right
here, the Fibonacci golden pocket, and
the 786. As well as if we pull all the
volume, we have confluence with the
value area low. So, what does that mean?
That means if we're looking at this
objectively here, I would say in the
context of a bullish divergence on the
weekly time frame, which we absolutely
have, in the context of a confirmed
bullish divergence on the twoe time
frame, which we actually have, in the
context of the daily giving us a
confirmed bullish divergence, looking
like it's setting up now for another
trigger wave continuation pattern, I
would say that this area right down here
is what I like to call where we're
looking for the big one, right? The big
trade. All right. In fact, I'm going to
label this right now. The big
one. All right. The bygon. The bygon.
You can see right here it says by gone.
All right. This is the bygone trade that
we're looking for. Let bygones be
bygones. We come down. We swipe the
liquidity from here. We get a bounce.
And here's the thing. If we actually do
make a higher low here, where would my
target be? Obviously, target one needs
to be $68,000 at the top of the local
range, right? We're basically looking
for a long from the bottom of the range,
and then we're looking to take profits
at the top of the range. But here's what
I'm thinking here. Given the bullishness
of the weekly, the two-weekly, and the
daily, if we reclaim $68,000, then I
would say we could very easily get
vacuum sucked up to value area high of a
macro range. I'm talking $74,000. This
would be my final target for this bygone
trade. Now, of course, this is a trade
only to be taken if we come down to the
area and we see bullish signs on the
chart. We get bullish confirmations and
all that kind of stuff, guys. And look,
if you want to join the Casper crew
where we give the trades in the moment,
I let people know in the moment what I
am doing, what I am looking for, taking
the juiciest trades, and go to
jasonaspertrading.com.
Also, guys, if you want to trade Bitcoin
and all coins, I'm currently trading on
Antarctic decentralized exchange as well
as Bitbase and Blowfin. All of these
exchanges will give you exclusive VIP
level fees. and Bitbase and Blowfin.
We're giving away $2500 every single
week to all of you guys who are trading
on the exchange using my link. All
right, so make sure if you're interested
to sign up for those juicy goodness
things. This is what I'm looking at for
Bitcoin. And of course, what about short
trades, you might ask? What if you're
feeling ultra bearish? Well, is there a
short trade to be had? Now, you could
make the case that the back test of this
PC is a valid short trade. Stop loss
above here targeting back down to the
low. You could make that case, but for
me, I would prefer to wait until higher.
I would prefer to wait until we come up
to the $68,000 level and see if we can
actually get a fake out of this. And if
we get a fake out of that, then we have
ourselves a beautiful potential swing
short trade on our hands with our stop
loss above wherever we come up to. And
then of course, our target would be all
the way back down in my opinion to make
a new low. And so that's kind of how I'm
looking at the charts right now. All
right, so the guys that's it for this
video. Make sure to like, subscribe,
click the bell for notifications. May
God bless all of you in the name of
Jesus Yeshua, the Messiah. Pray you and
your families are super blessed. And
I'll see everybody in the next video.
Peace.